[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "CD", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RB", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "And do we expect any of the victims to either attend or make any kind of statement themselves?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "Well, Piers, I'm learning from sources that one of the three victims will actually be making a statement here tomorrow, an impact statement.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "And in the end, we don't expect that he will receive anything other than a very, very lengthy prison sentence and will be unlikely to ever come out again, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CC", "MD", "VB", "RB", "TO", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "Right, this is not discretionary.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last week", "today"], "LOCATION": ["Stockholm"]}, "docId": "130731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "CC", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "From all you know from both Gina's side and her family and what you've heard of the others, do any of these young women who've been through this awful ordeal have any kind of sense of this -- they call the Stockholm syndrome where they feel a strange affection to their captor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "-NONE-", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "Well, if you listen to any of the court hearings from last week, the prosecutor did come out and say that there was some Stockholm syndrome and also in the report that they released today that the doctor also said that he believes all three girls are experiencing that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gina"], "LOCATION": ["Stockholm"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "Michael Hughes, what do you make of this video when you saw it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "Well, I believe that the deputy made a very vital mistake.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Hughes"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "EX", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "What kind of life will Ariel Castro face in prison, do you think, given the scale, the depravity of his behavior?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "MD", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "Oh, my prediction there will be a conspiracy within the inmates to get him.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ariel Castro"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 200, "question": "Do you still see him as a potential danger and threat to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "Not in a physical way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michelle Knight"]}, "docId": "130731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "What advice would you give these young women who've been through a decade of hell like this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "-NONE-", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "I mean, I was listening, I was getting teary-eyed once you're reading the story of that letter from Michelle Knight.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "If you'd been able to do a victim statement to O.J. Simpson, what would you have said to him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "Oh, you'd have to bleep me for the next 45 minutes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["O.J. Simpson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "Is this just for domestic e-mails or -- or is this for international e-mails or -- or both?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", ":", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", ":", "CC", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "Both.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ":"], "qSentId": 334, "question": "Well, what part of the -- what part of this -- what part of this don't you want to talk about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "WP", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "WP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "I wonder what...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "What part of which document that's come out don't you want to talk about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "WDT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBP", "RP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "I suppose it's the specifics of some of the programs.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "Do you feel comfortable as an American citizen that the enemy potentially know too much about what the American government can and can't do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "WP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "MD", "CC", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "I can tell you, I've been an investigative reporter for a long time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Glenn", "Glenn"]}, "docId": "130731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", ":", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "Piers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "Yes, Glenn -- yes, Glenn.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jeffrey"]}, "docId": "130731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "He somehow kept it secret from them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "No, they don't, Jeffrey.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "Is there a limit to what kind of material people with the kind of access that Edward Snowden had should be allowed to put out there before it crosses a line?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "TO", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "Oh, of course, there's always limits on that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Edward Snowden"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", ":", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "What is your reaction to it having seen it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "VBG", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "The -- the film that we see tomorrow night is a -- it's a good collection of -- of movies that were easily obtained from the national archives.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Richard Nixon"]}, "docId": "130731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "...is the biggest misconception about him that maybe persist to this day given your knowledge of him?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "Well, for the most part, right now, I see most of what's been told about Richard Nixon has been with some -- with a prejudice going through a filter.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "But did -- did Richard ever privately apologized to you, as his brother, for -- for what he had done?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", ":", "VBD", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", ":", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "He didn't need to.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Richard"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "On \"America's Got Talent\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "``", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "But tell me, is he entitled to it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "By law, he is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "But if you actually end up killing an unarmed teenager, isn't that the very least it should happen to be that maybe you don't get -- given back your gun?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "VBN", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "Not if you're found not guilty.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marc"]}, "docId": "130731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "Kristen Soltis, are you comfortable with George Zimmerman wandering around with this gun?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "I agree with Marc.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kristen Soltis", "George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "I think pretty extraordinary, wouldn't it, if A-Rod gets banned for life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "Yes, but it will be extraordinary, but it will be necessary as well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "WRB", ":", "WRB", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", ":", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "Kristen, are you a baseball fan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "I am much more of a football fan, where -- where issues about performance-enhancing substances are not -- not nearly as prevalent.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kristen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "Cheating is overstating is, though?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBZ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "It is cheating.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["99 percent"], "LOCATION": ["Central Park"]}, "docId": "130731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "So who are you cheating?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "So 99 percent of the people in Central Park are mugging people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "Is that fine?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "No, because by definition, it's still mugging.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "Because they're all pumped with steroids, therefore it's not cheating?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "It's a level playing field, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lance Armstrong"]}, "docId": "130731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "TO", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "IN", "NN", "RBS", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 552, "question": "So you then would defend Lance Armstrong?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 553, "answer": "Yes, I would say that Lance Armstrong is sort of being hung out to dry as the exception, when in fact most cyclists were doing it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lance Armstrong"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130731pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "The fact that everybody else is cheating makes it absolutely not cheating?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "VBG", "NNS", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "And the league sanctioned it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]